Well if you look at the blue line, it seems like its close to failing.
如果你看看这条蓝色的线 似乎它是失败的
It's too close to two of the points.
它太靠近这两个点了
If we were to pertobate it minimally, it would misclassify one or more points.
如果我们想要最小化误差 它会误分一个点到多个点
The yellow line though seems to be nicely spaced, and
然而这条黄色的线似乎是一个更好的划分
as far as it can from all the points.
考虑到它能够来自于所有的点进行划分
So it seems like the best line is the yellow line.
所以 似乎最好的线是这条黄色的
Therefore, if you said the yellow line, we agree.
因此 如果你选这条黄色的线 我们都是赞同的
And now the question is, how do we find this yellow line?
现在的问题是 我们如何能够找到这条黄色的线？
Well before finding the yellow line,
在找这条黄色的线之前
let's actually find a measure that tells us that the yellow line is better.
让我们事实上来找一个度量方式 它可以告诉我们黄色的线更好
So the first observation is that these points far away from the boundary,
那么 第一个观察的事情就是这些远离边界的点
didn't matter much to our decision.
它们对于我们的决定并不重要
So let's forget about them, and
所以让我们忘掉这些点
only consider the points close to the boundary.
只考虑那些里边界近的点
Actually, what we really have to focus is the distances from the points
事实上 我们真正要关注的是点到两条
to the two lines.
直线的距离
And what tells us that the yellow line is better?
什么让我们知道了黄色的线更好呢？
Well the yellow line is better because somehow it's farther from the points
这条黄色的线更好是因为不管怎么样 它都比蓝色的线
than the blue line.
离这些点更远
So we can just look at these four distances and notice that the smallest
那么 我们能够仅仅观察这四个点的距离 注意到这个距离中
of those four distances, is our measure of how close the line is to the points.
最小的距离就是我们度量点离直线到底有多近
This means that what we have to consider then is the minimum
这意味着我们必须要考虑的就是
of the four distances.
这四个距离的最小值
That's our measure of how close the line is to the points.
那是我们度量线离点到底有多近的方式
We'll call this measure the distance.
我们称这个度量为距离
So we conclude that the yellow line is better.
所以我们得出结论 黄色的线更好
Because the minimum for all these distances is larger for
因为在黄线中 这些距离中最小的距离
the yellow line, than for the blue line.
比蓝线中最小的距离大
So this is the function we need to work with, the minimum of the four distances.
这就是我们需要处理的函数 这四个距离中的最小值
And our goal is to make that minimum as large as possible.
我们的目标是使得这个最小值尽可能的大
In other words, we need to maximize the distance.
换句话说 我们需要最大化这个距离
And how do we maximize this distance?
我们能够怎么最大化这个距离呢？
You guessed it, with gradient descent.
你猜对了 使用梯度下降
There are also other methods we can use which we will learn during the class.
这里也有着其他的方法能够使用 我们之后的课上会学到
This method is called support vector machine.
这个方法叫做支持向量机
The word support comes from the fact that the points close to the boundary
这个词 支持 是因为靠近边界的点被称为支撑
are called the support.
这个事实